i have been a big fan of travelling
manali hoya
malaysia i am always ready to go on
exciting trips but because of pandemic
i have not been able to travel
i will fulfill all my travel
to go on a world tour and the first
destination on our list is
before i turn 75
i want at least 10 stamps on my passport
but to fulfill all my travel goals post
retirement
i realized that i will have to plan my
finances
that will take care of my monthly
expenses
and also help me fulfill my travel goals
presenting a retirement plan specially
designed for your needs
icici prove guaranteed pension plan
flexi
this plan is designed for people between
the age of 45 to 60 years and looking to
save for their retirement
the plan lets you invest small amounts
of money for a period of 15 years and
ensures a guaranteed income for life
so restart your life post retirement on
your own terms with icici pro guaranteed
pension plan flexi
one option this plan offers is the
single life with booster payouts in
addition to a guaranteed regular income
this option gives you booster payouts
that help you achieve your retirement
goals such as going on a vacation or
starting a hobby without worrying about
finances
key benefit of the plan
fifty percent of the premiums you invest
will be given to you in five
installments starting from the fifth
policy year after the completion of the
deferment period in the form of booster
payout the icic approved guaranteed
pension plan flexi also offers multiple
benefits
regular income with regular savings
choice of 7 annuity options as per your
needs
[Music]
unique options like accelerated health
boosters and booster payouts that
provide a periodic lump sum payout to
take care of your healthcare and
lifestyle needs
one percent additional annuity for
existing icici prudential life insurance
customers
save the date feature to receive your
income on the date of your choice
top-up facility to increase your income
by paying an additional premium
loan facility
to get access to money when you need it
[Music]
you